playspan.com 2008-12-17

# PlaySpan

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information collected (1) through the Playspan website, at corp.Playspan.com (the "Website"), and (2) through our Services and Client software. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy, are defined in the Playspan Marketplace Agreement corp.playspan.com/marketplaceagreement, into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated.

"Personal Information" is non-public information about you that is personally identifiable to you like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. "Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect, use, and disclose Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. User Consent

By submitting Personal Information through the Website, our Services, or the Client, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. 

## 2\. Collection of Information

**Personal Information You Provide to Us**

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website and the use of our Services. Whenever we collect Personal Information from you, we will make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. We collect the following types of data when you register: email address, physical contact information, credit card information, PayPal account information, in-game character and inventory information (including avatar data and game use data), user name and password, and demographic information. If the information you provide cannot be verified, we may ask you to send us additional information (such as your driver license, credit card statement, and/or a recent utility bill or other information confirming your address), or to answer additional questions online to help verify your information. When you contact us by sending us an e-mail (for example), we will collect your e-mail address and any information contained in the message you send us. 

If we offer a contest or sweepstakes relating to the Services, we may collect Personal Information in connection with it and we may state (in connection with the contest or sweepstakes) additional or different privacy practices that apply to such Personal Information. 

**Personal Information Collected Via Technology On the Website**

As you navigate our Website, certain information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like uniform resource locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed. This type of information is collected to better understand how you use our community and make the community and the Services we provide more useful to you.

An Internet protocol address or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track IP Addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly.

**Personal Information Collected Via Technology Through the Service**

As you use the Service (including through the use of the Client), we will collect information about your use of the Services, the listings you make, the bids you make, and transactions you enter into, including information about the Virtual Good involved, amount paid, date, and time. We will associate this Service-use information with your Personal Information. 

If you have accounts on multiple different games, we will collect information about your transactions related to all of those games.

**Personal Information We Receive From Other Sources**

We receive Personal Information from the applicable game providers about your in-game account and the Virtual Goods you choose to sell. If you choose to sell a Virtual Good, the game provider will provide us the details of that Virtual Good. 

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone or fax, or from third parties that provide services for us in connection with the Service. We will associate this information with your Personal Information. For example, we may receive information about your creditworthiness and about transactions that you have entered into in connection with other marketplaces. 

## 3\. Use

Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience in our Marketplace. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; 
  * customize, measure, and improve our services and the Sites' content and layout; 
  * tell you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. 

We store a PayPal credential in our systems so that, once you log into the Playspan Services and your PayPal account has been verified, you need not also enter your PayPal password.

## 4\. Disclosure of Personal Information

We may, and you authorize us to, share your Personal Information with:

  * our game provider partners and members of our corporate family;
  * service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards); 
  * other third parties to whom you ask us to send your information, or about whom you are otherwise notified and do not request to opt out of such sharing;
  * other users of the Marketplace, in connection with a dispute;
  * law enforcement or other governmental officials, if required by law or in response to a request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity;
  * other business entities, should we plan to merge with, sell our assets to, or be acquired by that business entity (should such a combination occur, we will send you notice and an opportunity to opt out if your personal information would be used contrary to this policy). 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to keep the Marketplace (and games connected to the Marketplace) free from bad actors, we may disclose your Personal Information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

We may disclose any Personal Information as permitted or required by law, to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. 

Playspan will not sell, rent or release your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without giving you notice and a chance to opt out.

We may make such disclosures in this Section about you as a consumer, a customer, or as a former customer. 

## 5\. Public Activity

Your User ID is displayed throughout the Marketplace and is therefore available to anyone using the Marketplace. All of your activities on the Marketplace will be traceable to your User ID. Other users can see your bids, items that you have purchased in the past, items for sale, storefronts, feedback, ratings and associated comments, and so on. Notices are sent to other community members regarding suspicious activity and policy violations on the Services and refer to User IDs. Therefore, if you associate your name with your User ID, the people to whom you have revealed your User ID to will be able to personally identify your Marketplace activities.

The Services enable you to share Personal Information with third parties. We cannot guarantee that the other users of the Marketplace will respect your privacy as provided in this Privacy Policy. To help protect your privacy, we allow other users only limited access to your contact, shipping and financial information in order to facilitate your transactions.

## 6\. Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about Users who are under the age of 13.

## 7\. Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

You can see, review and change most of your Personal Information by logging into the Services. Generally, we will not manually modify your Personal Information because it is very difficult to verify your identity by phone. You must promptly update your Personal Information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it. 

Upon your request, we will close your account as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. However, we do retain Personal Information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Marketplace Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. 

When you receive newsletters or promotional emails from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving such communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the instructions in the applicable newsletter or email. Make sure to set your Playspan notification preferences so we can communicate to you as you prefer. Despite your indicated preferences regarding promotional e-mail and text messages, however, we may send you administrative e-mails or text messages regarding the Service or notices of any updates to our Service Agreement or Privacy Policy. 

You may also opt out, by sending an email to [support@playspan.com](mailto:support@playspan.com) with a title of "Opt Out" of our disclosure of your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties (other than disclosures permitted by law). 

## 8\. Security 

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States and overseas. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your Personal Information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your Personal Information that they collect from the Services. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private. 

## 9\. Third Parties

This Privacy Policy addresses only the use and disclosure of Personal Information that Playspan collects about you. If you disclose Personal Information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers, sellers, or game providers, different rules may apply to their treatment of the information you disclose to them. Since Playspan does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

## 10\. Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@playspan.com](mailto:support@playspan.com)

## 11\. Privacy Policy Updates

As part of the Marketplace Agreement, this Privacy Policy is subject to occasional amendment, in accordance with the terms of the Marketplace Agreement.

_This Policy was last updated March 13, 2008._
